<comments name="window">
  <comment id="title"><![CDATA[
	@fileOverview A file to define the constructor and methods of the jindo.$Window() object
	@name window.js
	@author NAVER Ajax Platform
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="desc"><![CDATA[
	The $Window() object wraps a window object provided by a browser and provides various methods to handle it.
	
	@class jindo.$Window
	@keyword window
	@filter desktop
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="constructor"><![CDATA[
	Creates the $Window() object.
	
	@constructor
	@param {Hash+} oWindow The window object wrapped by the $Window() object
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="sign_value"><![CDATA[
	The $value() method returns the original window object.
	
	@method $value
	@return {jindo.$Window} The window object
	@example
		$Window().$value(); // Returns the original window object.
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="resizeTo"><![CDATA[
	The resizeTo() method resizes the size of a window as much as the size specified. The specified size means full size window including frame. Therefore, actual size of content to be shown could be different depending on browsers and settings. The security settings of some browsers may prevent the window from being resized beyond the current resolution of the screen. In this case, the window size can be smaller than the value specified (unit: pixels).
	
	@method resizeTo
	@param {Numeric} nWidth Width of a window
	@param {Numeric} nHeight Height of a window.
	@return {this} 창의 크기를 변경한 인스턴스 자신
	@see jindo.$Window#resizeBy
	@example
		// Resizes the current width to 400 and height to 300.
		$Window.resizeTo(400, 300);
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="resizeBy"><![CDATA[
	The resizeBy() method resizes the size of a window as specified. To increase window size, enter a positive integer; to decrease, enter a negative integer (unit: pixels).
	
	@method resizeBy
	@param {Numeric} nWidth The width of a window to increase or decrease
	@param {Numeric} nHeight The height of a window to increase or decrease
	@return {this} 창의 크기를 변경한 인스턴스 자신
	@see jindo.$Window#resizeTo
	@example
		// Increases the width as much as 100 and height as much as 50.
		$Window().resizeBy(100, 50);
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="moveTo"><![CDATA[
	The moveTo() method moves a window to a specified position. Coordinates are based on the upper-left corner of a window including frame (unit: pixels).
	
	@method moveTo
	@param {Numeric} nLeft The x coordinate of a window to move 
	@param {Numeric} nTop The y coordinate of a window to move 
	@return {this} 창의 위치를 변경한 인스턴스 자신
	@see jindo.$Window#moveBy
	@example
		// Moves the current window to (15, 10).
		$Window().moveTo(15, 10);
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="moveBy"><![CDATA[
	The moveBy() method moves a window by a specified number of pixels in a certain direction (unit: pixels).
	
	@method moveBy
	@param {Numeric} nLeft The number of pixels of a window to move horizontally. The window moves to right with a positive integer and left with a negative integer.
	@param {Numeric} nTop The number of pixels of a window to move vertically. The window moves to down with a positive integer and up with a negative integer.
	@return {this} 창의 위치를 변경한 인스턴스 자신
	@see jindo.$Window#moveTo
	@example
		// Moves the current window to left by 15 pixels and down by 10 pixels.
		$Window().moveBy(15, 10);
  ]]></comment>
  <comment id="sizeToContent"><![CDATA[
	The sizeToContent() method resizes the size of a window to fit the content size in a document.
	
	@method sizeToContent
	@param {Numeric} nWidth Width of a window
	@param {Numeric} nHeight Height of a window
	@return {this} 창의 크기를 변경한 인스턴스 자신
	@see jindo.$Document#renderingMode
	@remark There are several restrictions.<br>
		<ul class="disc">
			<li>This method must be executed after the document is completely loaded.
			<li>The size of a window must be smaller than that of a document; otherwise, the size of a document cannot be measured.</li>
			<li>The body size must be specified.</li>
			<li>This method does not work as intended in Opera version 10 for the Mackintosh environment and Internet Explorer version 6 and higher, Opera version 10, and Safari version 4 for Windows when the DOCTYPE of an HTML is Quirks.</li>
			<li>It should be executed in the parent window if possible. If a part of the child window is hidden because display is out of range, it is regarded as content not being exist in Internet Explorer. For this reason, the area decreases as much as the size of the hidden content.</li>
		</ul><br>
		You can fix the issues described above by specify parameters yourself.
	@example
		// A function to open a new window and automatically resize the size of the window to fit its content.
		function winopen(url) {
			try {
				win = window.open(url, "", "toolbar=0,location=0,status=0,menubar=0,scrollbars=0,resizable=0,width=250,height=300");
				win.moveTo(200, 100);
				win.focus();
			} catch(e){}
		
			setTimeout(function() {
				$Window(win).sizeToContent();
			}, 1000);
		}
		winopen('/samples/popup.html');
  ]]></comment>
</comments>
